<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_3487416217"
         name="Fix Representative"
         description="Fix Representative&#13;&#10;Nexus link : https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1702&#13;&#10;NB: Please note the Workshop Mod could receive less regular updates than the Nexus Mod&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Fix Representative&#13;&#10;This mod aim to force faction representative spawns. Or maybe you're a modder and don't want to bother about representative relocation ?&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;What it does ?&#13;&#10;Works on all valid registered factions since v2 - Vanilla, DLC and mods, as soone as the factions is registered in md.$FactionData&#13;&#10;There is an exclude rule on XENON (for obvious reason) and DUKES BUCCANEERS which is meant to be added by a story plot, not from the gamestart&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Each time you start a new game or load one (normally,) an mdscript will run an check if there is any missing faction representative. For example, this can happen if you use a mod that modify sector or cluster, or just if the game messed up and you didnt noticed it before the promotion.&#13;&#10;Some factions are less impacted than other. But for faction like Free Families, the representative is randomly placed on a whard, shipyard or equipment dock in FRF sectors, many things can happen that prevent the representative spawn.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This is when this script mod come to rescue you, the ForceReprensentative script dispatch the &quot;Missing Representative Task Force&quot;, aka **MRTF**.&#13;&#10;They will search for the representative and place it on a station of the targeted faction.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Technically ?&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;    The script will check existance of representative.&#13;&#10;    If a representative is missing, the script will check if the faction is active.&#13;&#10;    Then the script will try to reset HQ location and notify the game that there is a problem.&#13;&#10;    If the game don't solve the problem, we take things at hand&#13;&#10;    We will search for a big station (wharf, shipyard, equipment dock) to make the representative spawn on&#13;&#10;    If none : The script will abort, you have an other problem&#13;&#10;    If there is one : We update the default faction HQ location and the script will spawn the representative &#13;&#10;    The script will also create a room for him to sit in.&#13;&#10;    Then it will update the game data to let it know that a new representative is here.&#13;&#10;    TADA&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Install&#13;&#10;use Vortex or install it manually, the common way, can be done anytime, save game compatible (the script will run when you load the game)&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Uninstall&#13;&#10;Can be removed anytime, the remove fixrepresentative in Vortex or in your extensions directory&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Redistribution and modification&#13;&#10;BSD 2-Clause License&#13;&#10;Copyright (c) 2025, laryakan&#13;&#10;You are free to use, modify and redistribute any code or assets of mine&#13;&#10;which is not directly extracted from the game as soon as you mention the&#13;&#10;above Copyright.&#13;&#10;A link to my github is provided below. A little mention is all I ask.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;github : https://github.com/laryakan/fixrepresentative&#13;&#10;nexus : https://www.nexusmods.com/x4foundations/mods/1702&#13;&#10;nexus user : https://next.nexusmods.com/profile/Laryakan"
         author="Laryakan"
         version="211"
         date="2025-05-25"
         save="false"
         lastupdate="1748169690"/>
